This is an AI-enabled license plate
这是一个具备人工智能功能的车牌
reading surveillance camera, and in a
识别监控摄像头，而
convoluted way, the US's federal
美国联邦
Immigration and Customs Enforcement
移民和海关执法
Agency, more commonly known as ICE, has
局（通常被称为 ICE）通过一种复杂的方式
been able to access its data. This
获取了它的数据。
despite that the town whose police
尽管
department operates this camera,
运营这台摄像头的
Glenwood Springs, is about as far from
格伦伍德斯普林斯镇的警察局对美国移民及海关
supportive of ICE as any. Glenwood voted
执法局（ICE）的态度极其冷漠。 格伦伍德
two to one for Kamala Harris in the 2024
在 2024 年大选中以二比一的票数支持卡马拉·哈里斯，
election and is home to a large
并且拥有大量的
immigrant population with about a third
移民人口，其中约有三分之一的
of residents speaking Spanish within
居民在家中说西班牙语
their household. It's also in Colorado,
。 科罗拉多州也出现了这种情况，
whose majority blue voter base supported
该州的大多数民主党选民支持
the passage of a statewide law
通过一项全州法律，
explicitly prohibiting local police
明确禁止地方警察
departments from sharing data or
部门
cooperating with federal immigration
与联邦移民
authorities. But while this camera is
当局共享数据或合作。 虽然这台摄像机
operated by the local police department
由当地警察局操作，
and primarily used by the local police
也主要由当地
department, it's not actually owned by
警察局使用，但它实际上并不属于当地警察局所有
them. It's owned by a fast-growing
。 它隶属于一家名为 Flock Safety 的快速发展、由风险
venture capital-backed startup called
投资支持的初创公司
Flock Safety. The town then pays an
。 然后，该镇
annual fee of 37 and 1/2 thousand
每年支付 37500 美元的费用
dollars to be able to access its data,
才能访问其数据
[music] and that data is apparently
（音乐），而这些数据显然
useful. Through the included software
很有用。 通过配套的软件
suite, they're able to go back in time
，他们可以回溯过去，
and check where, when, and if a
查看
particular vehicle passed through their
特定车辆何时何地经过他们的
streets or add a license plate to a hot
街道，或者将车牌号添加到
list to get an alert when it appears,
黑名单中，以便在黑名单出现时收到警报，
allowing for the occupants' arrest.
从而逮捕车内人员。
Internal logs show the department uses
内部记录显示，该部门
the cameras just about daily to
几乎每天都会使用摄像头来
investigate anything from assault to
调查各种案件，从袭击、
stalking to sex offenses. And Glenwood
跟踪到性犯罪。 格伦伍德
PD purports these searches have been
警察局声称，这些搜查行动
instrumental in a number of successful
在许多成功案件中发挥了重要作用，
cases like arresting a gang member from
例如逮捕了一名驾驶
California in a stolen vehicle, a wanted
被盗车辆的加州帮派成员、一名
felon suspected of elder abuse, or a
涉嫌虐待老人的通缉重罪犯，以及一名
from Oregon.
从俄勒冈州引诱儿童到该镇的恋童癖者。
What makes Glenwood's cameras more
格伦伍德的摄像头
useful than most is the fact that
比大多数摄像头更有用的地方在于，
Interstate 70 passes through the town,
70 号州际公路穿过该镇，这
meaning [music] thousands of cars on
意味着每天都有成千上万辆
journeys both long and short drive
长途和短途汽车
through their view each day.
驶过它们的视野。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; That's why police departments from
这就是为什么全国各地的警察部门都
around the country want access to their
希望获得他们的
data. There's every chance a local
数据。 很有可能，
suspect from just about anywhere fled
来自任何地方的当地嫌疑人都
via Interstate 70 in an attempt to get
沿着 70 号州际公路逃跑，试图
far away fast. So Glenwood opted in to
迅速远离此地。 因此，格伦伍德选择
data sharing agreements with police
与全国各地的警察部门签订数据共享协议
departments around the country.
。
Basically, for the press of a couple
基本上，只需按几个
buttons, other police departments could
按钮，其他警察部门就可以
now search Glenwood's data, and Glenwood
搜索格伦伍德的数据，格伦伍德也
could do the same with theirs. But,
可以用同样的方法搜索自己的数据。 但美国移民及海关执法局（
that's how ICE got in.
ICE）就是这样入侵的。
In January 2025 alone, internal usage
仅在2025年1月，内部使用
logs indicate that outside police
日志就显示，外部警察
departments accessed Glenwood's data
部门访问格伦伍德的数据达
516,892
516,892
times. A subset of these outside police
次。 其中一部分外部警察
departments do actively and openly
部门会积极公开地
cooperate with ICE, which explains logs
与美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 合作，这就解释了为什么会有这样的记录
like these. Explicit acknowledgement
。 明确承认
that HSI, ICE's investigative arm, is
美国国土安全调查局（ICE 的调查部门）正在
conducting a search using Glenwood's
使用 Glenwood 的数据进行搜查
data.
。
There's even indication that Glenwood's
甚至有迹象表明，格伦伍德的
data might have been used to track
数据可能被用来追踪
political dissent. In their October
政治异议。 在他们的 10 月份
logs, there are a number of searches in
日志中，记录了“
the days following the No Kings Day
反对国王日”
protest, a nationwide demonstration
抗议活动（一场
against the actions of the Trump
反对特朗普政府行为的全国性示威活动）之后几天的多次搜索，理由是
reasoning protest. Legitimate crimes do
抗议。 即使在
happen even at overwhelmingly peaceful
绝大多数情况下都是和平的
protests, but the reasoning logged by
抗议活动中，也确实会发生合法的犯罪行为，但
police departments was not one, meaning
警察部门记录的理由并非如此，
this at the least demonstrates their
这意味着这至少表明他们
potential to use Flock data in
有可能以
illegitimate ways. That's especially
非法的方式使用 Flock 数据。 尤其需要
true since there's really no standard as
注意的是，目前
to how much police departments, or even
对于警察部门甚至
individual officers, must share to
单个警员必须分享多少信息才能
justify why they're using Flock data.
证明他们使用 Flock 数据的合理性，并没有真正的标准。
instances each month where Glenwood's
每个月都有成千上万起案例，格伦伍德
Police Department has no idea what other
警察局根本不知道其他
agencies are doing with their data since
机构正在如何使用他们的数据，因为
those agencies log the reason for their
这些机构将搜索原因记录
search as something ambiguous like
为模糊不清的内容，例如
investigation, TBD, test, or the number
调查、待定、测试或数字
zero. These agencies could be doing
零。 这些机构可能会
whatever with Glenwood's data, and the
随意使用格伦伍德的数据，而
Colorado would have no idea.
科罗拉多州却毫不知情。
And whatever certainly has happened.
以及已经发生的事情。
law enforcement agencies. A police chief
执法机构内部个别不法分子滥用职权的先例比比皆是。 堪萨斯州一名警察局长
in Kansas was caught using Flock data to
被发现利用 Flock 数据
stalk his ex-girlfriend 228 times. A
跟踪他的前女友 228 次。 南卡罗来纳州
North Charleston, South Carolina officer
北查尔斯顿的一名警官也
did the same with his wife. One in Miami
对他的妻子做了同样的事情。 迈阿密的一名男子
did so with his girlfriend. [music]
和他的女朋友一起做了这件事。  [音乐]
One in Menasha, Wisconsin did with his
威斯康星州梅纳沙的一位男士和他的前任一起做了这件事
ex. The cases go on and on, and it's
。 这类案件层出不穷，
hardly surprising given so many of those
考虑到很多
caught don't even face legal action and
被抓到的人甚至没有面临法律诉讼，
are simply disciplined internally. And
只是受到内部纪律处分，这种情况也就不奇怪了。
of course, [music] these are only the
当然，[音乐]这些只是
cases that are caught, and given the
被发现的案例，而且考虑到
spotty tracking of Flock usage, there's
Flock 的使用情况跟踪并不完善，
certainly ample ability to fly under the
肯定有很多机会可以逃避
radar.
监管。
Now, eventually local residents in
最终，
Glenwood Springs got wind of ICE's
格伦伍德斯普林斯的当地居民得知了美国移民及海关执法局（ICE）
access to their local data and put
获取当地数据的情况，并向
pressure on the city council. Their
市议会施压。 随后，他们的
police departments then closed off
警察部门关闭了
outside Colorado, meaning in theory, ICE
科罗拉多州以外机构对该系统访问权限的通道，这意味着理论上，
should no longer have had access given
鉴于
the state law prohibiting cooperation
州法律禁止
with ICE, but still then, according to
与美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 合作，ICE 应该不再拥有访问权限，但据《
reporting in the Aspen Daily News, logs
阿斯彭每日新闻》报道，日志
show that two police departments within
显示科罗拉多州的两个警察部门
Colorado illegally shared data with the
非法与该联邦机构共享了数据
federal agency. In response, Glenwood
。 作为回应，格伦伍德
entirely, but still then, the city's
完全切断了外部对该系统的控制，但即便如此，该市的
attorney stated that the terms of their
律师表示，他们
contract with Flock meant they quote,
与 Flock 签订的合同条款意味着他们
"Can't completely control what Flock
“无法完全控制 Flock 如何
does with data from Glenwood's system."
处理来自格伦伍德系统的数据”。
And there's precedent supporting the
而且已有先例表明，
idea that the data's still not secure.
数据仍然不安全。
Three hours down the road, Denver
三个小时车程之外，丹佛市在得知
after it came out that the city's data
该市的数据在
authorities against their wishes or
未经其同意或
knowledge as part of a pilot program.
不知情的情况下，作为试点项目的一部分与联邦移民当局共享后，终止了与 Flock 的合同。
And in Glenwood, even if the police
在格伦伍德，即使
department's cameras are successfully
警察局的摄像头成功地
walled off from the outside world, that
与外界隔绝，但这
doesn't mean that ICE can't get access
并不意味着美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 就无法获取
to Flock safety data from the town.
该镇的 Flock 安全数据。
This is the local Lowe's Home
这是当地的劳氏家居
Improvement store, and here, at the
建材商店，在这里，在
entrance to its parking lot, are even
其停车场入口处，还有
more Flock safety cameras. These cameras
更多的 Flock 安全摄像头。 这些摄像头
are operated and used by the store
由商店自行操作和使用
itself. Unlike the local police
。 与当地警察局不同
department, Lowe's doesn't publish its
，劳氏公司不公布其
logs, it doesn't say who's got access to
日志，也不说明谁可以访问
its data, it's collecting a database of
其数据，它正在收集
every single car that enters its lot,
进入其停车场的每一辆车的数据库，
and the public has absolutely no idea
而公众完全不知道
what it's doing with that data. It's
它正在如何使用这些数据。 这
just one of thousands of Flock safety
只是全国各地成千上万个 Flock 安全摄像头中的一个，这些摄像头并非由
by public agencies that must answer to
必须对选民负责的公共机构运营
their constituents, but by private
，而是由私人
companies, meaning they could act as a
公司运营，这意味着它们可能成为美国移民及海关执法
backdoor for ICE to surveil the
局 (ICE) 监视
movements of Americans even in
美国人行踪的后门，即使在
non-cooperative states [music] and
不合作的州和
municipalities.
市政当局也是如此。
Now, in recent polling, a majority of
最近民调显示，大多数
Americans have indicated distrust in
美国人对美国移民及海关执法局（ICE）表示不信任
ICE. So, even if Flock Safety is not a
。 因此，即使 Flock Safety 不是
system the agency [music] created, their
该机构（音乐）创建的系统，他们
access to local surveillance data is a
获取本地监控数据也
growing cause of concern. Plenty,
日益引起人们的担忧。 很多
perhaps most police departments have not
警察部门，或许大多数警察部门都没有像
received the pressure that Glenwood's
格伦伍德警察部门那样承受如此大的压力，他们
has and are still sharing data with
仍然会与
essentially any agency that asks. Any
任何提出要求的机构共享数据。 任何
database is only as secure as its
数据库的安全性都取决于其
weakest link, and there are some very
最薄弱的环节，而这个数据库存在一些非常
weak links with this one,
薄弱的​​环节，
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]这
&gt;&gt; meaning ICE now has fairly open access
意味着美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 现在几乎可以完全访问覆盖
to an effectively nationwide network of
全国的
license plate surveillance cameras. All
车牌监控摄像头网络。
they need to do is find one friendly
他们只需要找到一个友好的
local police department. But, of course,
当地警察局即可。 当然，
many of ICE's surveillance tools don't
ICE 的许多监控工具并不
require roundabout access. Many were
需要绕道而行。 许多产品都是
designed specifically for the agency's
专门为该机构设计的
use. In any of the endless videos
。 在无数
documenting tense, sometimes violent ICE
记录紧张、有时甚至暴力的移民执法局
arrests or confrontations, there's an
逮捕或对抗的视频中，
increasingly common sight: agents
越来越常见的一幕是：执法人员
holding a phone up to a person's face.
将手机举到被逮捕者的脸上。
this photo reveals it. This isn't the
这张照片揭示了它的具体用途。 这不是
iPhone's camera app. It's a proprietary
iPhone的相机应用。 这是
one developed specifically for use by
专为
federal immigration agents called Mobile
联邦移民执法人员开发的专有软件，名为 Mobile
Fortify. Here it can be seen in action.
Fortify。 这里可以看到它的实际应用。
This agent is attempting to use a Border
这位特工正试图使用​​边境
Patrol variant of it to identify this
巡逻队的变体来识别
hearing at a federal courthouse [music]
在纽约联邦法院等待移民听证会的这个人。[音乐]
in New York. If the agent scan is
如果特工扫描
successful, he'll see the individual's
成功，他将看到该人的
name, date of birth, nationality,
姓名、出生日期、国籍、
immigration status, and whether a judge
移民身份，以及法官是否
has already ruled that they should be
已裁定将其
deported, potentially giving [music] the
驱逐出境，这可能会给
agent probable cause for an arrest. Of
特工提供逮捕的合理理由。
course, like any facial recognition
当然，和所有面部识别
software, this app is only as good as
软件一样，这款应用的效果也取决于
its imagery database. For that, ICE
其图像数据库的质量。 为此，ICE
siphons data primarily from Customs and
主要从海关和
Border Protection, another agency under
边境保护局获取数据，海关和边境保护局是国土安全部下属的另一个机构，
the DHS umbrella that deals with
负责
processing people at legal ports [music]
处理合法入境口岸的人员
of entry. Over recent years, CBP has
。 近年来，美国海关与边境保护局
dramatically ramped up their use of
大幅增加了
biometrics, giving them a massive, yet
生物识别技术的使用，从而建立了一个庞大的、
still growing database of identity data
仍在不断增长的数据库，其中包含了
on Americans [music]
美国人
and non-Americans alike. You see,
和非美国人的身份数据。 你看，
previously, unlike many countries, the
以前，与许多国家不同，
US had no formal [music] exit
美国没有正式的（音乐）出境
immigration controls. Rather, airlines
移民管制。 相反，航空公司
shared data with authorities, which gave
与当局共享数据，这使得当局能够
them a mostly accurate picture of who
大致准确地了解谁在
left the US and when. Today, though, an
何时离开了美国。 不过，如今
increasing number of US airports are
越来越多的美国机场都
equipped with a biometric gates that
配备了生物识别闸机，可以
against their passport photos when
在登机时扫描人们的面部并将其与护照照片进行匹配
boarding a plane. This is both more
。 这是
accurate and new imagery of an
对个人更准确、更新颖的描述
individual. Towards the end of 2025, DHS
。 到 2025 年底，美国国土安全部
announced that these exit immigration
宣布，这些出境移民
checks would become universal, meaning
检查将全面实施，这意味着
being installed at any airport with
所有有
international flights, dramatically
国际航班的机场都将安装生物识别闸机，这将大幅
increasing the amount of data the agency
增加该机构收集的数据量
will collect. While photos from these
。
gates of US citizens are said to be
据说，美国公民在这些关卡拍摄的照片会
deleted within 12 hours, non-citizens'
在 12 小时内删除，而非公民的
photos are kept for up to 75 years and
照片则会被保存长达 75 年，并
put into a file that can be accessed by
放入一个可通过
ICE's Mobile Fortify app. This applies
ICE 的 Mobile Fortify 应用程序访问的文件中。 这适用
to much of the imagery that identifies
于识别
those with legal status in the [music]
在美国具有合法身份的人的大部分图像
US, while Mobile Fortify also has access
，而 Mobile Fortify 还可以访问
to ICE's case management system and the
ICE 的案件管理系统和
FBI's [music] National Crime Information
FBI 的国家犯罪信息
Center to provide imagery of individuals
中心，以提供
more likely to generate probable cause
更有可能产生
for arrest.
逮捕理由的个人的图像。
ICE agents use Mobile Fortify a lot, and
ICE 特工经常使用 Mobile Fortify，
this internal document indicates why.
这份内部文件说明了原因。
Quote, ICE does not provide the
引用：ICE 不提供
opportunity for individuals to decline
个人拒绝
or consent to the collection and use of
或同意收集和使用
biometric data/photograph collection.
生物识别数据/照片的机会。
Basically, agents are allowed to use the
基本上，代理人可以
app on anyone, anywhere, [music] at any
随时随地以任何理由对任何人使用该应用程序播放音乐
time, for any reason. This is a source
。 这会带来一些
of problems, since, to put it bluntly,
问题，因为坦白地说，
the app isn't very good. In October
这个应用程序不太好用。
2025, ICE agents conducted a major
2025 年 10 月，美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 特工
operation in the immigrant-heavy
在
agricultural town of Woodburn, Oregon.
俄勒冈州伍德伯恩这个移民众多的农业小镇开展了一次重大行动。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 一起与美国移民及海关执法局 (
alleged unlawful actions by ICE during
ICE) 在
this raid gives a glimpse into how
此次突袭行动中涉嫌非法行为相关的诉讼中的证词，让我们得以一窥
Mobile Fortify actually functions in the
Mobile Fortify 在实际应用中的运作方式
field. An officer scanned the face of
。 一名警官仔细查看了
one of the detained individuals and,
其中一名被拘留者的面部，并
quote, "It came up to a very like a
说道：“这很像一个
similar person. I wasn't sure if it was
人。我不确定是
her or not." The match was for a person
不是她。” 这场比赛的参赛者
named Maria, so he called out Maria and
名叫玛丽亚，于是他喊出了玛丽亚的名字，但玛丽亚
given no response, verbal or otherwise,
没有回应，无论是口头上的还是其他方面的，于是
he scanned her face again. Then the app
他又仔细打量了她的脸。 然后，该应用程序又
matched with an entirely different
匹配到了完全不同的
person. In the deposition, the officer
人。 在作证时，这名警官
was then asked what his probable cause
被问及逮捕这名女子的合理理由
was for arresting this woman, the
是什么，这是
American law enforcement must pass to
美国执法部门
lawfully arrest an individual. The
依法逮捕个人必须达到的宪法规定的门槛。
officer responds, quote, "I believe she
警官回应道：“我认为她
was in the country illegally because
非法入境，原因有二：
one, the primary language she used that
首先，
I heard her use was Spanish, and then to
我听到她主要使用的语言是西班牙语，而且她
interact with everyone else was Spanish.
与其他人交流时也使用西班牙语。
She became a possible match on my facial
她的面部识别结果与我的系统匹配成功
recognition system."
。”
Courts have repeatedly ruled that the
法院一再裁定，
language an individual speaks alone
仅凭一个人所说的话
cannot be used as probable cause,
不能作为合理理由，这
meaning the court legal probable cause
意味着
the officer might have been using to
警官可能用来
justify the arrest was the Mobile
证明逮捕合法性的法院合法合理理由是 Mobile
Fortify app. And of course, the officer
Fortify 应用程序。 当然，这名警官
himself admitted that the app
本人也承认，该应用程序
misidentified the woman at least once,
至少错误识别了该女子一次，甚至
potentially twice, meaning he was solely
可能两次，这意味着他完全
relying on knowingly faulty information
依赖于明知有误的信息
as the basis of his probable cause. This
作为其合理理由的依据。 此案
case is still ongoing and it's not
仍在进行中，
publicly known what happened to the
公众尚不清楚被
misidentified woman, but what is known
错误识别的女子最终遭遇了什么，但已知的是，在
is that across the country, ICE agents
全国范围内，移民执法局的特工们
are using this faulty app as the basis
正在使用这款有缺陷的应用程序作为
of their probable cause. While facial
他们进行调查的依据。 虽然面部
recognition might be highly accurate in
识别在受控环境中可能非常准确
a controlled environment, the settings
，但
in which agents are using Mobile Fortify
特工使用 Mobile Fortify 的环境
are far from that. Lighting is
远非如此。 光线
inconsistent, the camera is unstable,
不稳定，摄像机不稳定，
individuals are moving their head to
人们会移动头部以
evade scans. It's the exact situation
躲避扫描。 这正是
where facial recognition struggles.
面部识别技术难以应对的情况。
But beyond the problem of the app
但除了该应用程序
functioning as a false premise to
被用作
justify unlawful detentions, the app is
非法拘留的虚假前提这一问题之外，该应用程序的
also being used in a manner entirely
使用方式也
different than intended. Increasingly,
与预期完全不同。 人们越来越频繁地
federal agents have been seen holding
看到联邦特工举起
their phones up, capturing imagery of
手机，
protesters in a manner consistent with
以与
the use of Mobile Fortify. In settings
使用 Mobile Fortify 一致的方式拍摄抗议者的图像。 在像
like Minneapolis, anti-ICE protesters
明尼阿波利斯这样的地方，反对移民执法局的抗议者
were overwhelmingly white,
绝大多数是
English-speaking individuals, meaning
讲英语的白人，这意味着
the agents would not likely suspect them
执法人员不太可能怀疑他们的
of irregular immigration status.
移民身份不合法。
Clearly, people vulnerable to legal
显然，那些可能被美国移民及
deportation by ICE are unlikely to go
海关执法局合法驱逐出境的人不太可能去
out into such a setting. So, why would
到这样的环境中。 那么，为什么
agents be using Mobile Fortify against
特工们会使用移动防御系统来对付
these protesters? Well, while there's no
这些抗议者呢？ 虽然无法
way to know for sure, this internal
确定，但这份内部
document hints at a theory.
文件暗示了一种可能性。
Unlike the airport biometric data, this
与机场生物识别数据不同，该数据
says that imagery from Mobile Fortify is
表明，即使照片中的人是美国公民，Mobile Fortify 的图像也会
retained for up to 15 years, even if the
保留长达 15 年
pictured individual is a US citizen.
。
What we do know with certainty is that
我们确切知道的是，
when an agent uses Mobile Fortify, a
当特工使用 Mobile Fortify 时，该应用程序
so-called encounter log is created by
会创建一个所谓的遭遇日志，
the app where an individual's photo and
其中会将个人的照片和
name is tied to the time, location, and
姓名与拍摄的时间、地点和
circumstance of its capture. So, that's
情况关联起来。
to say, if an individual's image is
也就是说，如果某人
captured at a protest, ICE now has an
在抗议活动中被拍到照片，那么美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 将在
electronic record for the next 15 years
接下来的 15 年内拥有
that that individual was there. And
该人曾出现在现场的电子记录。 而且，也有一些
there's anecdotal evidence of what the
轶事证据表明
federal government does with this
联邦政府是如何处理这些
information. This court filing related
信息的。 这份与
to the agency's actions in Minnesota
该机构在明尼苏达州的行动有关的法庭文件
includes an allegation by a woman acting
包括一名女性的指控，该女性以
as a so-called legal observer, following
所谓的法律观察员的身份跟踪
DHS vehicles and documenting their
国土安全部车辆并记录其
actions. She alleges that the agent,
行动。 她声称，该特工
quote, "stopped in the road, making it
“停在路中间，使
impossible for her to proceed." The
她无法继续前进”。
name, despite not having volunteered her
尽管该女子并未主动提供姓名，但警官还是叫出了她的
name, threatened her with arrest if she
名字，并威胁说如果她
continued, and warned her that they had
继续下去就要逮捕她，还警告她他们有
facial recognition technology.
面部识别技术。
Three days later, she got an email
三天后，她收到一封电子邮件，
saying that the TSA had revoked her
称美国运输安全管理局 (TSA) 已撤销了她的
precheck status, the widespread program
预检资格。预检是一项广泛应用的计划，
that allows for expedited airport
允许
screening for so-called trusted
所谓的“可信
travelers. Having been a member of the
旅客”快速通过机场安检。 作为该项目的成员
program for 14 years, one can reasonably
已有 14 年，人们有理由
assume that the two events were
认为这两件事是有
connected. While this appears to be an
关联的。 虽然目前看来这只是一起
isolated incident for now, what it
孤立事件，但它
demonstrates is that on the street
表明，在国土安全部内部，街头
facial recognition data is flowing
人脸识别数据正在流向
elsewhere within DHS. And even if
其他地方。 即使
protesters yet, given what we know about
目前还没有针对反移民执法局抗议者的大规模系统性报复行动，但鉴于我们对
how MobileFortify works, there's a
MobileFortify 运作方式的了解，
reason to believe that this is already
有理由相信这种情况已经在
field. It's believed that when an
实际环境中小规模发生了。 据信，当
individual is identified using
使用 MobileFortify 识别出某人后
MobileFortify, agents can see if another
，执法人员可以看到其他人是否
already used the app on that individual.
已经使用该应用程序识别过该人。
That means they can see the indicators
这意味着他们可以看到
that someone was previously at an
某人之前是否参加过
anti-ICE protest, meaning it acts as a
反移民及海关执法局（ICE）的抗议活动，这意味着它充当了
database of dissent. Unlawful and
异议数据库的角色。 联邦特工非法和
arbitrary detention of protesters by
任意拘留抗议者的现象
federal agents is well reported and
屡见不鲜，而且十分
widespread, and the app could act as a
普遍，该应用程序可以作为
decision-making tool of who agents want
特工决定将目标锁定在哪些人身上的决策工具
to target. Now, with each additional
。 现在，随着美国移民及海关执法局（
surveillance tool ICE is known to
ICE）掌握的监视工具越来越多
possess, the details get fuzzier. For
，细节也变得越来越模糊。
example, we know they have these,
例如，我们知道他们有这些，
stingrays. These are typically included
黄貂鱼。 这些设备通常包含在价值
as part of a half-million-dollar
五十万美元的
vehicle-based cell phone surveillance
车载手机监控
system, and they work by effectively
系统中，其工作原理是有效地
spoofing a real cell signal. Cell phones
欺骗真实的手机信号。 手机的
are designed to constantly switch to the
设计使其能够不断切换到
strongest signal, typically from the
最强的信号，通常是来自
closest tower, meaning any cell phone
最近的信号塔的信号，这意味着任何
near a stingray device will connect.
靠近 Stingray 设备的手机都会连接上。
Next, the device is able to capture this
接下来，该设备能够获取
connected cell phone's IMSI number, a
已连接手机的 IMSI 号码，这是一个与
corresponds to the user's carrier
用户运营商
account. Through a subpoena, court
帐户对应的唯一数字组合。 通过传票、法院
order, or warrant, ICE is then able to
命令或搜查令，ICE 可以
gain access to carrier records and draw
获取运营商记录，并将
a link between an IMSI number and a
IMSI 号码与
user's identity. Considering how
用户身份联系起来。 考虑到
powerful stingrays are as a surveillance
黄貂鱼作为监视
tool, ICE's policies only allow targeted
工具的强大威力，美国移民及海关执法局的政策只允许在获得搜查令的情况下进行有针对性的
use with a warrant. Essentially, [music]
使用。 从本质上讲，[音乐]
it must have a directed purpose towards
必须具有明确的目标，即
finding a specific device or individual.
找到特定的设备或个人。
Of course, this can be legitimately
当然，例如，这
useful for determining whether a
对于确定
targeted individual is at home or at
目标人物是在家还是在
work, for example. There is, however, a
工作场所，可能非常有用。 然而，美国移民及海关执法局 (
long, long history of ICE ignoring its
ICE) 无视
own policies and using stingrays without
自身政策，在没有搜查令的情况下使用“黄貂鱼”搜查令，这由来已久
a warrant. It's so pervasive, in fact,
。 事实上，这个问题非常普遍，甚至还有
that there's a whole Inspector General
一份完整的监察长
report about the issue. But, there's
报告专门讨论这个问题。 但是，
also some circumstantial evidence of the
也有一些间接证据表明，该
agency even more flagrantly breaking
机构更加明目张胆地违反
policy and using stingrays [music] in
政策，在非目标的大规模监视行动中使用“黄貂鱼”（音乐），
operations, capturing and collecting the
捕获和收集
target area. Analysis of cellular
目标区域内任何人的 IMSI 号码。
signals at a July 4th, 2025 anti-ICE
对 2025 年 7 月 4 日
protest in Seattle, Washington, found
在华盛顿州西雅图举行的反 ICE 抗议活动中的手机信号进行分析后发现，存在
anomalies consistent with IMSI catcher
与 IMSI 捕获器使用一致的异常情况
use, meaning the agency might have been
，这意味着该机构可能一直在
using devices to gather a log of all the
使用设备来收集所有
devices and therefore individuals
设备以及在场人员的日志
present at that demonstration. License
。 车牌
plate readers, mobile fortify, and
识别器、移动防御系统和
stingrays [music] really are only the
Stingrays（音乐）真的只是
tip of the iceberg. ICE also has access
冰山一角。 美国移民及海关执法局 (ICE) 还拥有
to a massive software suite of digital
一套庞大的数字
surveillance tools that are increasingly
监控工具软件，这些工具正日益实现
automating their investigative work,
调查工作的自动化，从而
allowing for more personnel to stay out
使更多的人员能够留
in the streets rounding up more
在街头抓捕更多的
individuals for deportation. There's
人进行驱逐出境。 还有一些
also all the tools we don't know about.
我们尚不了解的工具。   美国
ICE rarely volunteers information about
移民及海关执法局很少主动提供有关
their surveillance systems, so what we
其监控系统的信息，因此我们所
know comes from leaks, court documents,
知道的都是来自泄露的信息、法庭文件、
mandatory disclosures, and observation.
强制披露和观察。
With $75 billion in additional funding
随着
recently approved by Congress, nearly
国会最近批准了 750 亿美元的额外拨款，未来几年美国移民及海关执法局 (
tripling ICE's annual budget over the
ICE) 的年度预算将增加近三倍
next few years, the depth and breadth of
，该机构系统的深度和广度
the agency's systems are sure to expand
肯定会
increasingly fast. This is, of course, a
越来越快地扩展。 这当然是
threat to immigrant rights. Many of
对移民权利的威胁。
these tools just aren't that effective.
这些工具很多都不太有效。
They have massive error rates, but ICE
这些工具的错误率很高，但ICE并
has little motivation to improve these
没有动力去改进这些
ineffective tools since for their
无效的工具，因为就其
purposes, they're effective. They can be
用途而言，这些工具是有效的。 它们可能被
used as a pretext for unlawful arrests
用作借口，在没有正当理由的情况下非法逮捕
of those lacking legal status without
那些缺乏合法身份的人
legitimate probable cause. It is
。
difficult for the agency to gain
该机构很难获得
legitimate probable cause on
针对个人的合法合理理由
individuals, so it's simply easier for
，因此
them to ignore people's constitutional
他们干脆无视人们的宪法
rights, detain them, then investigate
权利，拘留他们，然后调查
their residency status. With no one in
他们的居住状况。 如今，
power in the business of challenging
在权力中心，没有人敢质疑美国移民及海关执法局（
ICE's lawfulness these days, this just
ICE）的合法性，所以这种做法
works. And many Americans have chosen to
行之有效。 许多美国人选择
not concern themselves with the
不去关心
immigrants so long as doing so hastens
移民的宪法权利和人权，只要这样做能够加快
the administration's progress towards
政府实现其让
America. For those people, however, the
美国更加同质化的目标。 然而，对于这些人来说，美国移民及海关执法局（
means towards ICE's ends should still be
ICE）实现其目标的手段仍然值得
a source of concern. The agency has
关注。 该机构在
American people. One that has happened
美国民众遭受大规模监控的过程中发挥了重要作用。 这种情况在历届
government wide across administrations,
政府中都普遍存在，
but one that ICE has helped hasten.
但美国移民及海关执法局（ICE）加速了这一进程。
Traditionally, the US public has been
传统上，美国公众
uniquely wary of domestic government
对国内政府监控抱有特殊的警惕性
surveillance. Polling indicates that
。 民意调查显示，
Americans are far more concerned by this
美国人对此
than the average European, for example,
比普通欧洲人更加关注，
and are generally content with a certain
并且通常乐于接受
compromise in security in exchange for
在安全方面做出一定妥协，以换取
increased privacy. One of the most
更高的隐私。
important parts of the Constitution is
宪法最重要的部分之一是
the protections against unreasonable
保护公民免受无理
search and seizure. ICE is challenging
搜查和扣押。 美国移民及海关执法局（ICE）正在挑战
this by effectively searching everyone
这一做法，在
without warrants in hopes of finding
没有搜查令的情况下对所有人进行搜查，希望从中找到
useful info. Many might consider the
有用的信息。 许多人可能认为这些措施
surface level of their use worthwhile,
表面上是有价值的，
but there's ample overwhelming evidence
但有大量压倒性的证据表明，
that the agency ignores or changes
该机构会
policy when convenient, hides their
在方便的时候忽视或改变政策，
methods from the public, and generally
向公众隐瞒其方法，而且通常
can't be trusted to do surveillance the
不能相信他们会以
so-called right way.
所谓的正确方式进行监视。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; At times these fast and loose methods
有时，这些快速而随意的方法
make the agency more efficient at
使该机构在
removing immigrants, meaning some might
驱逐移民方面更加高效，这意味着有些人可能会为这些方法
justify them, but at other times it
辩护，但有时，它使
normalizes an America where people in
美国成为这样一种常态：
power have the ability to know where you
掌权者能够随时知道你在哪里
are, who you know, what you look like,
、你认识谁、你长什么样
and what you're doing at any given time.
以及你在做什么。
This power is already being abused, but
这种权力已经被滥用，但
the same abuse that's currently being
目前
targeted at immigrants and protesters
针对移民和抗议者的这种滥用行为，
can later be directed towards simply
以后可能会针对任何
anyone. America is becoming a
人。 美国正在变成一个
surveillance state, and too many aren't
监控国家，但太多人并不
concerned because the victims so far are
担心，因为到目前为止，受害者
primarily those they've been told are
主要是那些被告知是
the enemy.
敌人的人。
Many of these forms of digital
许多形式的数字
surveillance are effectively
监控实际上是
unavoidable, but not all. For example,
不可避免的，但并非所有形式都是如此。 例如，
your internet service provider likely
您的互联网服务提供商可能会
keeps some amount of data on your
保留一些关于您
browsing history, and in the US, [music]
浏览历史记录的数据，而在美国，
government if they have a proper
如果政府持有有效的
subpoena or warrant. While this is not
传票或搜查令，这些数据可能会被移交给政府。 虽然这
too much of a concern for most, it's
对于大多数人来说并不算什么大问题，但这
just one of almost endless examples of
只是
where our sponsor NordVPN would be
我们的赞助商 NordVPN 能够派上
useful. Turning their VPN on creates an
用场的无数例子之一。 启用他们的 VPN 会在
encrypted tunnel between yourself and
您和
their VPN server, [music] and unlike
他们的 VPN 服务器之间创建一个加密隧道，[音乐] 并且与
many internet service providers, Nord
许多互联网服务提供商不同，Nord
VPN doesn't keep any usage data that
VPN 不会保留任何使用数据，
even if they were compelled to. They've
即使他们被迫这样做，也不会将这些数据交给政府。 它们
even been independently reviewed by PwC
甚至经过普华永道
and Deloitte to assure that this is
和德勤的独立审核，以确保其
really true. But beyond evading
真实性。 除了规避
government surveillance, Nord VPN has
政府监控之外，Nord VPN 还有
plenty other practical applications,
许多其他实际用途
too. [music] For example, it can also
。  [音乐] 例如，它还可以
get around government firewalls. If
绕过政府防火墙。 如果
you're traveling or living in a place
您正在旅行或居住在
where certain sites are blocked, Nord
某些网站被屏蔽的地方，Nord
VPN allows you to virtually redirect
VPN 可以让您
your traffic through one of their
通过其位于任意
servers in any number of countries,
多个国家的服务器之一来虚拟重定向您的流量，从而
allowing you to browse a more open
让您浏览更开放的
version of the internet. The same works
互联网版本。 这同样
for geo-blocking on websites. If your
适用于网站的地理位置屏蔽功能。 如果您的
streaming service isn't allowing you to
流媒体服务
watch something based on where you're
因您浏览的地区而不允许您观看某些内容
browsing from, Nord VPN can fix that
，Nord VPN
with just a few clicks. It's also great
只需点击几下即可解决此问题。 它对
for day-to-day internet security. Their
日常网络安全也很有帮助。 他们的
threat protection pro system
威胁防护专业系统会
automatically blocks dangerous ads,
自动拦截危险的广告、
pop-ups, or websites, reducing the risk
弹出窗口或网站，从而降低
of getting malware. The uses go on, but
感染恶意软件的风险。  VPN 的用途还有很多，但
the point is that, in my opinion,
重点是，在我看来，
[music] a VPN is a crucial tool for any
对于当今任何互联网用户来说，VPN 都是一个至关重要的工具
internet user today. I find myself using
。 我发现自己
Nord VPN for something on pretty much a
几乎每天都会用到Nord VPN
daily basis. If you'd like to sign up,
。 如果您想注册，
they're offering an exclusive deal for
他们为 Wendover 的观众提供独家优惠
Wendover viewers, including 4 months
，
extra when you go to
访问
nordvpn.com/wendover
nordvpn.com/wendover
or click the link in the description.
或点击说明中的链接，即可额外获得 4 个月的使用时间。
And it's worth giving them a shot since
而且由于
it's risk-free with their 30-day
他们提供 30 天
money-back guarantee.
退款保证，所以值得一试，因为没有任何风险。